ご視聴ありがとうございました
Unforgivable!
You unforgivable humans!
I will invade...
that putrid surface of yours!
shinryaku shinryaku shinryaku shinryaku shinryaku shinryaku ika musume (kyun!)
Squid Girl, invade!
ご視聴ありがとうございました
SHINRYAKU!
IKA MUSUME
FFFpeeps Presents
kira kira na umi to kaze kagayaku atoriumu
The sea's radiant, the breeze's blowing, and the atrium's sparkling
minna de atsumatte hajimemasho hajimemasho
Everyone, get together! Let's begin!
hora hora soko no kimi, wagamama na taido de
Hey you over there! What's with that attitude?!
ochitari itakushitara ikandesho ikandesho
It's no good if you fall and hurt yourself!
honto wa motto yasashii kimochi wo motteru deshou anata mo
I'm sure you're compassionate as well, right?
ご視聴ありがとうございました
hitoribocchi mo umi no heiwa mo
Even if I'm alone
I'll protect the sea and everyone's happiness!
ichigen kigen mo shiawase mo mamorimasu!
(Uuuuu sanhai!)
Uu~~~  Here we go!
ii kanji muteki ni susume ii kanji mujaki ni susume
Great! Invincible Squid Girl, go! Great! Innocent Squid Girl, go!
higashi no shima ittara otakara ippai daishouri! (waii!)
You'll find treasure in the island to the east!
お宝いっぱい大勝利
いい金も棒にすすめ
ii kanji mubou ni susume ii kanji muchuu ni susume
Great! Reckless Squid Girl, go! Great! Irresistible Squid Girl, go!
いい金も銃にすすめ
単狂的 嬉しい
tanjouseki ureshii konomama tenka wo torenaika?
Yay, it's my birthday! Shall I just take over the world?
このまま天下を取れないか
shinryaku kouryaku keikaku seikou!
Invade! Conquer! Plan success!
侵略 攻略 計画 成功
侵略 攻略 ギト娘
shinryaku kouryaku ika musume (kyun!)
Squid Girl, invade and conquer!
侵略しないか?
Won't You Invade?
"Won't You Invade?"
侵略 攻略 ギト娘
Sis, is the yakisoba ready?
姉貴 焼きそばまだ?
上がったわよ アエコちゃん
It's almost done,
Eiko!
生ビールお待ちどうさま
Thanks for waiting. Here's your beer!
こっちもビール
I'd like some beer, too.
はーい
Okay!
人類よ、よく聞け
Listen carefully, you scumbags!
今からこの家を人類侵略の拠点にさせていただくでゲソ
Starting now, I will make this my home base, to invade and punish humanity.
恐怖で言葉が出ないようでゲソね
It seems you are too afraid to even speak, eh?
心配しなくてもお主たちを殺したりはしないでゲソ
You don't have to worry though, I won't be killing you humans.
雑用係としてコキ使ってやるでゲソ
At worst, you'll just become my servants!
はいはい、そこまで
All right, that's enough.
なんなんでゲソ、私をどこへ連れて行くつもりでゲソ
What's the matter?
Where are you taking me?
ひとつ聞くが、そのコスプレはなんだ
I have one question.
What's with that cosplay?
そういえば自己紹介がまだだったでゲソ
Oh yeah, I have yet to introduce myself.
私は海からの使者
I'm a messenger from the sea.
イカ娘でゲソ
I'm Ika Musume!
あれ、反応薄いでゲソ
Huh? What's with her?
なんでうちの店に
And why did you come to our shop?
海から一番近いから
Because it's the closest to the sea.
でゲソ、ここを拠点に人類侵略を進めるでゲソ
I'll make this my home base and invade humanity!
なんで人類侵略なんてするんだ
And why do you want to invade humanity in the first place?
決まってるでゲソ
That's obvious!
Those filthy humans have forgotten what the sea has given them...
人間どもは今まで海の恩恵を忘れて
私利私欲のために平気で海を汚してきた
and have been polluting the sea for their own gain.
私たち海の生き物にとって人類など百害あって一利なし
To creatures of the sea,
humans have done nothing but harm to us.
だから私が人類を懲らしめる
That's why I will punish them!
In order to protect the sea!
海を守るために
あれ
Eh?
わかった
I get it.
けど今日は急がないでゲソ
But we are busy today. We have work to do here, you see?
あ、忙しい
こっちも仕事があるんでな
またにしてくれ
Please come back later.
気をつけて帰れよ
Go back safely.
じゃあな
T-Thank you...
See ya...
あ、ああ、ありがとうでゲソ
ちょ、ちょっと待たないか
Hold it right there!
嘘やハッタリだと思ったら大間違いでゲソ
You thought I was lying back there, didn't you?
話を聞かないか
Listen to what I have to say!
はい、焼きそば
Here's the yakisoba.
3番テーブルにお願いね
Take these to Table 3, please.
醤油ラーメンは5番
The soy sauce ramen goes to Table 5.
ん?
や、焼きそば3番、ラーメン5番…
Yakisoba to Table 3...
焼きそば3番、ラーメン5番…
Ramen to 5...
I have no chopsticks...
箸がないんだけど
お冷やください
Ice water please.
同じやつ、おかおり
Another jug please!
油そばとヨーザ
I want some aburasoba and gyoza.
ちょ、ちょっと待つでゲソ
Please wait a minute!
かき氷1つ、いちごと練乳ね
Two shaved ice, one with strawberries and one with condensed milk!
ペペロンチーノ
ハイボール
Spaghetti pepperoncino!
A highball!
ハッピーネー、唐揚げとシューマイ
Namashirasu-don!
Some fried chicken...
生シラス丼
Got it!
わかったでゲソ
これ片付けてくれる?
Could you take these?
今やるでゲソ
I'll do it right away!
焼きそば2つ持ち帰りで
Two yakisobas to go...
Ice cream!
One more...
ヨーザさん、はい
アイスクリーム
Please hold onto our bags.
荷物お願いします
I'd like to borrow...
ごめんなさい、ごめんなさい、ごめんなさいでゲソ
もう借りたいんですけど
I'm sorry! I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
触るな!
Don't touch it!
ケガしたらどうするんだ
What if you cut yourself?
ったか危ないだろ?
That's dangerous you know.
そそうした私を叱ることなく
She didn't scold me for my blunder...
心配をしてくれるなんて
but was worried about me instead!
顔は怖いけど
She might look scary, but she's actually kind.
意外といい人じゃないか
ほら、ここはいいから料理運べ
Hey, I'll do this, so deliver the food.
Understood!
わかったでゲソ!
なんか違わないか?
Isn't this wrong?!
私は人類を侵略しに来たんでゲソ
I came to invade and punish humans!
バイトに来たんじゃないでゲソ!
I didn't come here for work!
はいはい、わかったわかった
Yeah, yeah, I got it, I got it.
働くつもりがないなら邪魔をしないで帰ってくれ
If you aren't here to work, then please don't bother us and go home.
遊びじゃないでゲソ!
I'm not fooling around!
私は本当に侵略を
I really came to invade-
侵略、侵略って簡単に言うけどな
It's not that easy, you know?
今日のうちの客、何人だと思う?
Do you know how many customers we have here today?
たくさん、いっぱい、大勢か?
It's full...
so it's...
many?
30人だ30人
It's thirty people, thirty!
たったそんだけの客もさばけないで
You can't even handle that many...
and you still think you will be able to invade all humanity?
人類を侵略できると思ってるのか?
侵略ってのはつまり
In other words, an invasion...
would mean ruling over 6.4 billion humans by yourself!
64億人の人間を
お前一人で
支配するってことだ
僕
Billions...?!
何人だと思ってたんだよ
How many did you think there were?
せ、1000人くらいだと思ってたでゲソ
I was thinking, about a thousand...
1000人ならなんとかなると思ってたのかよ
And you thought you could manage with a thousand people?
あとな、人類を敵に回すってことは
Also, if you make all humanity your enemy...
that would also mean you are making all the armies around the world your enemy.
世界中の軍隊を敵に回すってことだぞ
Do you think you can go against all that by yourself?
お前一人で相手できんのか?
軍隊ってなんでゲソ?
What's an army?
そっからかよ!
You don't even know that?!
じゃあ銃は?
What's a gun?
Ten?
ミサイルは?
銃
A missile?
味噌汁
Miso soup?
今日初めて地上に来たのに
It's the first time I've come to the surface...
そんなこと分かるわけないじゃないかー!
so there's no way I would know all that!
あっ
蚊一匹も死ぼつべきやけど
She can't even kill a single mosquito,
and yet she wants to invade humanity...
人類死んできた・・・
私の本気を見せてやるでゲソ
Well then, I'll show you my true power!
そこでゲソ
There!
どうでゲソ
How's that?!
私もやればできるのでゲソ
If I put my mind to it I can do anything!
恐怖と感動で声も出ないようではないか
Oh, you are so amazed that you're rendered speechless, aren't you?
よくも
How dare you...
うちの店の壁ぶち壊してくれたな
wreck our store's wall!
どの道私のものになるんだからいいじゃないか
This store is going to be mine either way, so it doesn't matter!
ならねえよ
Like hell it will!
お前のこれは自分の意思で動かしてるのか
These things of yours...
Can you move them as you wish?
そうでゲソよ
That's right!
シード
Speed!
パワー
Power!
イッチ
Range!
イパシー
Precision!
10本の触手は狙った獲物を確実に捕らえ
These ten tentacles will capture any prey
絶対に逃がさないでゲソ
and won't let it escape!
ま、イカの常識ってところでゲソね
Well, it's only normal for squids to do this, no?
超えてるっつのイカの常識
This is beyond normal for squids...
お前この家を拠点にしたいって言ってたの
You said you wanted to make this your home base right?
そうでゲソ
That's right!
いいぜ
Go ahead, then!
ほんとでゲソか
Really?!
なんで私が働かされなきゃいかんのでゲソ
ああ
Yes!
Why do I have to work here against my will?!
修理代
You'll be paying for the damages with those tentacles!
触手で払ってもらえないのか
もらうからなあ
あらあら新しいバイトさんね
I see, so we got a new employee, huh?
ゲソゲソ
イカ娘ちゃんこれ4番テーブルね
Ika Musume,
take this to Table 4, please.
Okay!
はいでゲソ
Stock some coke in the fridge, too.
ほらクーラーに貸しとけよ
今やるでゲソ
I will do it right now!
同胞じゃないか
Aren't You My Comrade?
"Aren't You My Comrade?"
I came here to invade them.
侵略しに来たのに
This isn't what I had in mind!
こんなはずじゃないでゲソ
気のせいでゲソか
Was it just my imagination?
うおーな視線を感じるでゲソ
I felt someone staring!
女いいね!
このうねうね
This twisting thingy is funny!
面白いね
ネutz
Twisting thingy?
私の触手はよくもそんな風に
How dare he humiliate my tentacles like that!
Ah it's moving!
ああ動く
変なの
This is so weird!
いかんなめられてるでゲソ
It's no good!
まずゲシャする seeming cool
He's looking down on me!
ここは一つ私の怖さを教えてあげようじゃないか
I'll show him how scary I can be!
面白い
It backfired?
That was fun!
もう一回やって
逆効果
Do it again, do it aga....
もう一回
Again, again!
そうでげそ
That's it!
遊んでやるから私の部下になるでげそ
I'll play with you, but you'll have to become my subordinate!
部下
Subordinate?
私は海からの死者イカ娘でげそ
I'm a messenger from the sea, Ika Musume!
私のことは隊長と呼ぶこと
You will now refer to me as "Boss" and respect me as one!
あとちゃんと敬語を使うでげそ
了解であります隊長
Understood, Boss!
This is just fine!
これはいいでげそ
早速地上を侵略するための作戦に取り掛かるでげそ
Let's begin our first mission to invade the world right away!
はい隊長
Yes, Boss!
まずはここを占拠するでげそ
We'll start by taking this place!
おう
突撃でげそ
Let's initiate the assault!
おう
何やってんだイカ娘
What are you doing, Ika Musume?
今から
Starting now, this place is all mine!
ここは私のものでげそ
今から
してたのかタケル
Oh, were you here, Takeru?
うん姉ちゃん
Yeah, Sis.
姉ちゃんってことは弟
Sis? Then... is he her younger brother?
僕この隊長の部下になったんだよ
I just became Boss's subordinate.
地上を一緒に侵略するんだ
We are going to invade humanity together!
うちの弟
Oh, with my brother...?
遊びでげそ
侵略ごっこのつもりだったでげそ
We were p-playing!
We were pretending to invade humanity!
部下にしてくれるって言ったのに
But you said you'll make me your subordinate!
人間の子供の相手はしてられないでげそ
I can't waste time dealing with human kids!
私は忙しいんでげそ
I'm busy right now!
イカ姉ちゃん
Sis!
人間の子供の相手はしてられないでげそ
Human kids won't do...
子供の相手は
That's it!
そうだ
What are you doing, Takeru?
何やってんだタケル
これでイカ息子に見えるかな
With this I could look more like a Squid Boy.
息子
Squid Boy... oh.
ああ
イカ娘ちゃんのあれね
Oh, you mean that thing on Ika Musume.
見分けがつかないほど完成度高いわ
It's so well done that I almost can't tell the difference.
むしろ小学生に作れてしまうほど簡単ということでは
It's just so simple that even a kid can make it.
あいつのことだから真似するんじゃないでげそ
Knowing her, though, she'll just go "Stop copying me~"
and get all angry about it.
とかって怒るんじゃないか
ほら怒らせた
See, she got mad.
そんなところで出たのかよ
I never thought I would meet a comrade in a place like this!
どこに会えるなんて
えええ
きっとお主も地上を侵略しに来たのでげそね
You came to the surface to invade as well, right?
そ、そうでげそ
Eh? Th-that's right...
もしかしてタケルだって気づいてない
Maybe she doesn't realize that's Takeru?
たぶんあのパーツさえあれば仲間と認識するのに十分なんじゃないかしら
Probably.
So that hat is enough to make her think he's one of them...
There is no time to waste. Let me explain my invasion plan!
さっそく今後の侵略計画を話そうじゃないか
ないか
Let's do it!
Currently I'm in charge of cleaning in that house.
今私はあの家の床掃除を任されているでげそ
つまり地盤はもう占拠したも同然
That means we've already occupied a secure base!
次は椅子テーブル方面に侵攻するでげそ
Next we'll advance to the chairs and tables!
仲間に会えてすごく嬉しいんだろうな
She seems pretty happy to have found a partner.
なのに僕本当は
But I'm just a...
I will assign you to take over the counter!
というわけでお主には主にカウンター方面を任せるでげそ
え、あ、い、いいんじゃないか
Yeah, th-that'll be fine.
ところでお主触手は
By the way... where are your tentacles?
あ、ちょ、ちょっと待っててくれないか
Wo-would you wait a little?
え、どうしたの
What's the matter?
あ、お姉ちゃんあのね
Sis, you see...
あ
ただいま、でげそ
I'm back...
よかったなお主、触手が生え変わって
That's great!
Your tentacles grew back!
よかった、ごまかせたわ
I'm so glad she fell for it.
よかったのかよ
You're happy about that?
しかしお主の触手は細くて元気がないのではないか
But still, aren't those tentacles kind of limp and lifeless?
ええ、そんなことないよ
Eh? It's nothing like that.
垂れ下がっているだけみたいだし、大丈夫でげそか
It looks like they're just hanging...
Will they be all right?
ちょっと待っててでげそ
Please wait a minute!
おお、なんと元気な触手ではないか
Wow, they seem all lively now!
これなら大丈夫でげそ
They'll be fine!
よし、さっそく今から出撃でげそ
Okay, now that's settled, let's start our mission!
え、今から
Eh?! Right now?
With the two of us...
二人もいれば案内へ、余裕でげそ
that place will be nothing!
ていうか、その安易な計画はどうなんだろう
Wouldn't a simplistic plan like that be a problem?
どこへ行くー
Where are you going?
せっかく
After...
ばれた
She found out!
After I finally found a comrade...
せっかく同胞に会えたのに、なんで突然死んだりするのでげそー
Why did he have to die so suddenly?!
ええ
いかねー、ちゃん
Sis...
You and I are no longer subordinate and boss!
おぬしとはもはや部下でも隊長でもない
また人間扱いに戻った
She's treating me as a human again.
うう、同胞よ
My dearest comrade...
うう
せめて
At least, you'll finally be able to rest in peace back where you belong.
故郷で安らかに
眠るでげそ
まあ、なんだ、ご苦労さん
Well...
Uhh...
You did well.
もう会いに来ないと
Farewell!
さらばでげそー
はーはーはー
Am I Not The Strongest?
"Am I Not The Strongest?"
最強じゃないか?
雨だとお店も静かね
The store is rather quiet when it rains.
どうした
What's the matter?
あそこにいる髪の毛の長い女は誰でゲソ
Who's that woman over there with the long hair?
ずっといただろうが
She's always been there.
それは知ってるでゲソ
I know that much!
お主やお主の弟と何か関係があるのでゲソか
Is she related to you and your brother?
気づいてなかったのか
Didn't you notice it before?
姉貴だ姉貴
She's our big sister.
千鶴って名前の
Her name is Chizuru.
姉貴
Big sister...
全然違うでゲソ
She's totally different from you guys!
お主はバイオレンスだし弟の方はうるさいし追っかけてくるし
You're so violent, and your brother is rather noisy and bothersome.
でもあれはなんだかバイオレンスもないしものすごくまともに見えるでゲソ
But she is totally different! She's not the violent kind, and seems normal!
バイオレンスで悪かったな
Well, I'm sorry for being so violent!
あらあらだめよ英子ちゃん
Don't be so rude.
イカ娘ちゃんをいじめちゃ
Don't pick on her.
やさしいでゲソ
She's so kind!
イカ娘ちゃん悪いけどこれ運んでくれる
Ika Musume!
Sorry to bother you, but could you please take this?
了解でゲソ
Got it!
今日は肌寒いでゲソ
Today is kinda cold...
お前なんてもん吐いてんだよ
What did you sneeze out just now?!
何を焦っているのでゲソ
Why are you so flustered?
イカスミを吐いただけじゃないか
All I did was cough up some squid ink.
溶けつかと思ったじゃねえか早く吹け
I thought you were vomiting blood! Wipe it off right now!
あらほんとイカスミだわ
Ah, this really is squid ink!
リアクション薄
Such a mild reaction!
しかも舐めた
And she licked it...
イカ娘ちゃんって本当にイカ気味なのね
You really are like a squid!
イカ気味ってなんだよ
What do you mean "like a squid"?
てかシャオンのイカ娘ちゃん
And how about taking a shower?
今日は浴びてきたらイカスミ臭いよ
Squid ink stinks, you know.
そうするわお店よろしくね
I'll do that.
Please take care of the store.
お主なら私を許すまい
You'd never forgive me for that, if it were you.
当たり前だ
Of course not!
お前のおかげでイカスミスパゲッティは当分食えないな
Thanks to you, I won't be able to eat squid ink spaghetti for a while.
イカスミスパゲッティ
Squid ink...
spaghetti?
人間どもはこれを食べるのでゲソか
Do humans really eat this?
だから目の前で吐くなっての
Don't do that in front of me!
ああそうだよスパゲッティと絡めて
But yes, we mix it into the spaghetti along with the squid!
イカの実と一緒に
まさか私を
Does that mean that I too...
誰が食うか
Who would eat you?
お主が食わずとも別の客が
Even if you wouldn't, other customers could...
人間がいないでゲソね
There aren't any humans around.
雨が降ってるからな
That's because it's raining.
雨が降ると人間がいなくなるのでゲソか
So when it rains, do people just vanish like that?
こんな天気の日に遊ぶ物好きはいないだろ
No one would want to go out in such weather.
今この辺りにいるのは
Right now, there's no one but
チズルとか
the quiet, black-haired Chizuru, the little brat Takeru,
言う事なし黒髪の女と
うざったい子供タケル
and that somewhat strong person in here.
それに少し強いが
そこにいるこいつだけ
ということは
That means...
Eat before you get eaten!
割れる前に食え
This is my chance to take control of this place!
この家を支配するチャンスでゲソ
今日こそ今日こそギャフンと言わせてやるでゲソ
Today, today at last, I shall pay back those who have mistreated me!
さてと私は掃除でもすっかのう?
Well then, I might as well do some cleaning...
イカ娘お前も手伝えよ
Ika Musume, you help out, too.
いやでゲソ
No way.
お前自分の立場が分かってんのか
Do you understand your position here?
それはこっちのセリフでゲソ
That would be my line!
人間の分際で偉そうに
Acting like that when you are nothing but a human...
私が何のために地上に来たと
Have you forgotten why I came to the surface?
思っているのでゲソ
Wasn't it for work?
アルバイトじゃないのか
人類制服でゲソ
It was to invade humanity!
その拠点としてまずこの家が必要
I first need this place as my base.
そのためには
For that to happen...
I gotta get rid of nuisances like you!
お主が邪魔のでゲソ
どういうつもりだ話せ
What are you thinking? Let me go!
口の聞き方に気を付けた方がいいんじゃないか
You should watch how you speak to me, don't you think?
Just a little twist and your body will...
こんなひとひねりでお主の体など
ああ何やってるのさ
What are you doing?
タケル危ない
Takeru, it's dangerous!
エルヒア姉ちゃん一人だけ楽しそうにして
You're so unfair sis,
having all the fun for yourself!
僕もイカ姉ちゃんと遊びたい
I want to play with her, too!
お前はパニック映画もそんな風に見るのか
Does it look like we're playing here?!
言わずとも同じ目に合わせてやるでゲソ
I'll do the same to you even without you asking!
Yay!
はーい
さてあとは一人
Well then, there's only one left.
招きに手を出す気か
Are you going to hurt my sister?
It's a waste of time to try to stop me!
止めても無駄でゲソ
今日の私は本気なのでゲソ
I'm totally serious today!
いや私たちを解放した方が身のためだと思うぞ
No, really, it would be better for you to let us go.
この状況でまだそんなこと言っていられるでゲソか
Still saying that when you are in this state?
だから私たちじゃなくてお前のためだって
It's not for us! It's for your own good!
Oh my, what's going on?
何事
来たでゲソね
So you came!
お主もおとなしく捕まって
Just stay there and be captured!
三人仲良く朽ち果てるでゲソ
You three can rot away together!
てい
Here!
で巫女を大変恥もってくろうってイタリア人には
ロスが壁に出るというよりも
しかもゲソがご飯の中に住んでると
You shouldn't fool around inside the shop. Right?
ゲソちゃんたちが寝るときに
ゲソに奇跡が見えない
ゲシャンゲシャン
私たちの姿を見守って
R-Right...
ゲソにお供えをする
It's good as long as you understand.
contra
えぇ
ポンポン
ゲシャンゲシャン
Okay, now apologize properly to both of them.
ギルヴギン
ゲシャンゲシャン
エルヒア姉ちゃんを連れて帰らないと
ごめんなさいでけしょ
I'm terribly sorry!
いいよ
It's fine.
楽しかったよ
It was fun!
だから言ったろお前のためだって
That's why I told you it was for your own good.
ところでイカ娘ちゃん
By the way...
なんか用意してる
She prepared something.
イカスミお願い
Squid ink please.
イカスミってこいつの
This girl's squid ink?
冗談だろ
ええ
You're kidding right?
Yes.
なんでだってイカスミじゃない
Why?
She's a squid, after all.
さっき私にかかった時
Do it just like when you sneezed on me.
ごめんなさいごめんなさいごめんなさいでけしょ
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm really sorry!
ううん違うの
No, no, it's not that.
なめてみたけど味は確かだったわ
I licked it and the taste was the real thing.
かけてもらっていいかしら
So could you put some of that on this,
イカ娘ちゃん
Ika Musume?
イカスミならいくらでもかけるでけしょ
I can give you as much as you want.
はい出来上がり
It's ready!
僕も食べる僕も
I want to eat, too!
はいエイコちゃんも
Here, Eiko, have some, too!
吐くとこ見せられて食え
How can I eat it after what I saw?
いいから
It's all right, so just try it.
食べてみなさい
うまい
Heavenly!
Squid Ink Spaghetti 500 yen
It's great!
泳いだ後に塩気のあるイカスミがたまらん
This salty taste of squid ink is just irresistible after a swim!
イカスミスパゲッティ
Squid ink spaghetti!
イカスミスパください
Squid ink spaghetti, please!
イカスミおかわり
One more squid ink spaghetti!
イカスミスパゲッティ
Squid ink spaghetti!
イカスミスパゲッティ二つ
Two squid ink spaghetti!
イカスミスパゲッティ
Squid ink spaghetti, please!
イカスミ持ち帰りで
Squid ink spaghetti to go!
Squid ink spaghetti!
大好評ね
イカスタ
It's become popular, hasn't it?
何も知らない客にはな
うん
For the customers who don't know the truth, yeah.
Yes.
おいあと4人前な
Hey, four more please.
持ってないでけそ
It's not coming out anymore...
もうこんな搾取ばかりのところにはいられないでけそ
I'm not going to stay here getting exploited like this!
イカ娘ちゃんお願いね
Ika Musume!
Pretty please.
お客様が待ってるの
Our customers are waiting.
はいいいでけそ
Yes, okay!
誰が一番怖いか
I guess she finally found out who the scariest one really is.
ようやく悟ったようだな
はい
waratteiru ima ga itooshikute
I'll treasure this moment, as I smiled
hitori ja nai to omotta
when I thought I wasn't alone
hajimari wa subete guuzen de
It all started by coincidence
sore wa kiseki no meguriai
That encounter was a miracle
ご視聴ありがとうございました
I fumbled when we first met
deatta koro wa tesaguri de
Demo kawasu kotoba ga ureshikute
But I was happy just to exchange a few words
dareka ga jibun no namae wo yobu
Someone calls my name
atarashii sekai ga mawari hajimeru
And a new world begins to turn
deatta koto
Meeting each other
shinjiru koto
Trusting each other
ご視聴ありがとうございました
atarimae no you de
It all seems so obvious
that it's difficult
sore ga muzukashii
waratteiru ima ga itooshikute
I'll treasure this moment, as I smiled
hitori ja nai to omotta
when I thought I wasn't alone
ご視聴ありがとうございました
I'm a messenger from the sea, Ika Musume!
Next time:
Won't You Play?
Won't You Celebrate?
Aren't You My Companion?
"Aren't You My Companion?"
"Won't You Celebrate?"
"Won't You Play?"
I'll subdue you if you don't watch it!